[
	{
		"question": "What is Launcher?",
		"desired answer": "a framework for running large collections of serial multithreaded applications known as High Throughput Computing (HTC)"
	},

	{
		"question": "How can users submit Launcher jobs?",
		"desired answer": "by creating a SLURM job script"
	},
	{
		"question": "How many tasks can be ran in a job?",
		"desired answer": "16 - 60"
	},
	{
		"question": "What are two useful parameters?",
		"desired answer": "$LAUNCHER_JID and $LAUNCHER_TSK_ID"
	},
	{
		"question": "What can I not use Launcher for?",
		"desired answer": "Matlab, ANSYS, or Mathematica jobs in parallel"
        },
	{
		"question": "What is $LAUNCHER_JID?",
		"desired answer": "the rank of the jobs listed in the job file"
	},
	{
		"question": "What does Launcher not support?",
		"desired answer": "MPI jobs"
	},
	{
		"question": "What is Launcher not used for?",
		"desired answer": "Matlab, ANSYS, or Mathematica jobs in parallel"
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the name of the newly developed tool based on Launcher?",
		"desired answer": "Launcher-GPU"
	},
	{
		"question": "What does $LAUNCHER_TSK_ID?",
		"desired answer": "the rank of the tasks (-n) running simultaneously"
	}
]
